A Guide to the Markle Foundation records, Accessions 1997-2008, Record Group 4 FA785
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant and Grantee Files, 1971-1999; 2; 52.48 Cubic Feet
  - Aspen Institute - Grant G94309 - Planning meeting for "Impact of Interactive Communications", 1993-1994 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    "Support of a planning meeting for a conference with the working title, 'The Impact of Interactive Communications Upon Belief, Behavior, and Governance During the Next Century'".
  - Aspen Institute - Grant G94330 - Forum on Communications and Society (FOCAS) charter membership, 1994-1996 (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Aspen Institute - Grant G95111, 1994-1998 (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Aspen Institute - Grant G97022, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    "To produce a roundtable forum for the Aspen Institute at the Jerusalem International Book Fair that will explore and asses the impact of the internet and other communications technologies on scholarly writing and academic publishing".
  - Aspen Institute - Grant G97102, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    "For charter membership in the Aspen Institute Forum on communications and Society (FOCAS), which will convene a series of conferences to address different issues relating to the societal impact of the international information infrastructure".
  - Aspen Institute - Grant G97228, 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 4-5)
    "To convene industry and policy leaders to address issues relating to the concept of universality of electronic communications".
  - Aspen Institute - Grant G98113, 1998-1999 (Box 57, Folder 6-7)
    "To conduct a series of three meetings and publish reports on public interest obligations of digital broadcasting".
  - Aspen Institute - "Democracy in the Information Age", 1992 (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Aspen Institute - General, 1972-1974 (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Aspen Institute - General, 1975 (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Aspen Institute - General, 1976 (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Aspen Institute - General, 1977-1978 (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Aspen Institute - General, 1979 (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Aspen Institute - General, 1980 (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Aspen Institute - General, 1981 (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Aspen Institute - General, 1982-1984 (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Aspen Institute - General, 1985-1987 (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Aspen Institute - General, 1988 (Box 59, Folder 2-3)
  - Aspen Institute - General, 1989 (Box 59, Folder 4-5)
  - Aspen Institute - General, 1990 (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Aspen Institute - General, 1991 (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Aspen Institute - General, 1992 (Box 59, Folder 8-9)
  - Aspen Institute - General, 1993 (Box 60, Folder 1-2)
  - Aspen Institute - Forum on Communications and Society (FOCAS), Second meeting, "Teaching and Learning Outside the Classroom", 1995 (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Aspen Institute - Michael Rice, 1987-1990 (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Aspen Institute - Fred Star, 1994-1996 (Box 60, Folder 5-6)
  - Aspen Institute - Fred Star, 1994-1996 (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Aspen Institute - State Telecommunications Regulation, 1988-1989 (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Aspen Institute - Telecommunications Policy, Regulation, 1987-1989 (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Aspen Institute - Television Criticism Cirriculum, 1976-1979 (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Aspen Institute - Workshop, "Impact of Interactive Communications on Beliefs and Behaviour During the 21st Century", 1994 (Box 61, Folder 5-6)
  - Association of American Colleges, 1971-1990 (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Association of American Medical Colleges, 1987-1989 (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Association of Governing Boards of Universities and Colleges, 1995-1996 (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Atlantic Telephone and Telegraph (AT&T), 1991-1994 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Atlantic Philanthropic Service Co., 1993-1996 (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Audience Assesment Ratings and Rates, 1988-1990 (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Ken Auletta, 1996 (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - B - General, 1989-1991 (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - B - General, 1992-1994 (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - B - General, 1995-1997 (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Al Balk, 1987-1991 (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Bank Street, 1987-1988 (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Barter, Honest Broker, 1987-1989 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Baruch College, 1997 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Philippe de Gaste Beaubien and Nan-b, 1993 (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Beepers and paging systems, 1987 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Bell Corp., Bell Atlantic, 1994-1995 (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Benton Foundation, 1981-1989 (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Benton Foundation, 1990-1996 (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Benton Foundation, 1993-1996 (Box 63, Folder 8-9)
  - Benton Foundation, 1993-1996 (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Charles Benton, White House Conference on Library and Information Service, 1998 (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Richard Bergland, 1983-1992 (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Berks Community Television, 1987-1992 (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Bertelsman Foundation, 1996 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Dick Block, 1987 (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Marshall Blonsky, "America by Design", 1980 (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Jay G. Blumler, 1987-1992 (Box 64, Folder 8-10)
  - Marjorie Blumenthal, 1997 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - David Bollier, 1988-1992 (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Borun Center for Gernotological Research, University of California Los Angeles (UCLA), 1989-1990 (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Boston Consulting Group, 1995 (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Boston University, 1976-1995 (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Brandeis University, 1993 (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Louis A. Branford, Public service Satellite Consortium, 1991 (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Peter Bratt - Cloudscan, 1990 (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Berkeley Roundtable on the International Economy (BRIE), 1998 (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - British Broadcasting Corporation (BBC), 1971-1992 (Box 65, Folder 10)
  - British Film Institute, 1992-1995 (Box 65, Folder 11)
  - British Telecom-Community Network, 1983-1991 (Box 65, Folder 12)
  - Broderbund Software, Inc., 1994 (Box 65, Folder 13)
  - Brody and Weiser - retreat, 1993-1995 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  - Brookings Institution, 1987-1996 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Brown University, 1983-1989 (Box 66, Folder 2-3)
  - Burson-Marsteller, Public Relations, 1994 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - C - General, 1989-1993 (Box 66, Folder 5)
  - C - General, 1994-1995 (Box 66, Folder 6)
  - C - General, 1996-1997 (Box 67, Folder 1-2)
  - Cable television - Misc., 1972-1992 (Box 67, Folder 3-4)
  - Cable television - Legal issues, conferences, 1986-1987 (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Cable television - Reports, 1988-1989 (Box 67, Folder 6)
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - Grant G92004, Democracy in America, 1991-1992 (Box 67, Folder 7)
    Support for "Democracy in America" programming.
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - Grant G92004, Democracy in America, 1991-1992 (Box 68, Folder 1-3)
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - Grant G92005, Election Project '92, 1992-1993 (Box 68, Folder 4-5)
    "To implement the Foundation's Election Project '92,?. to establish the 'Election Channel' during the 1992 presidential campaign".
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - Grant G92005, Election Project '92 - Financial, 1992-1993 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - Grant G92005, Election Project '92 - Publicity articles, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 2-3)
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - Grant G92005, Election Project '92 - Meetings, 1992 (Box 69, Folder 4-6)
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - Grant G92222, Consultants for CNN project, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 1-2)
    "To support CNN's 'Democracy in America' series through educational seminars and by means of promotional activities designed to bring the programs to the attention of the audience".
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - Grant G92222, Carter Center, International observation of U.S. elections, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 3)
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - Grant G92222, Electronic Citizenship meeting, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - Grant G92222, Project Vote Smart, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 5)
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - General, 1991 (Box 70, Folder 6)
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - General, 1992 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - General, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 1-2)
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - General, 1993-1996 (Box 71, Folder 3)
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - Press releases, 1992 (Box 71, Folder 4)
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - "Making of the President '96", 1995 (Box 71, Folder 5)
  - Cable News Network (CNN) - World Report, 1987-1988 (Box 71, Folder 6)
  - University of California, Berkeley - Grant G98112 - Conference on intellectual property and contract law in the information age, 1998-1999 (Box 71, Folder 7-9)
    "To conduct a conference on intellectual property and contract law in the information age".
  - University of California, Berkeley - Grant G98112 - Conference on intellectual property and contract law in the information age, 1998-1999 (Box 72, Folder 1)
  - University of California, Berkeley - General, 1971-1995 (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) - Grant G90213 - Paid political advertising, 1990 (Box 72, Folder 3)
    Shanto Iyengar, "To conduct research on paid political advertising".
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) - Grant G92109 - Paid political advertising, 1992-1995 (Box 72, Folder 4)
    Shanto Iyengar, "To conduct research on paid political advertising, and to hold a series of conferences in which campaign managers, candidates, scholars, reporters, and policymakers discuss the implications and consequences of televised advertising".
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) - Grant D93218 - Paid political advertising, 1993-1995 (Box 72, Folder 5)
    "In support of Prof. Shanto Iyengar's additional research on paid political advertising".
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) - Grant D94220 - Effects of interactive manipulation of videotaped evidence on credibility, 1994-1996 (Box 72, Folder 6)
    Patricia Greenfield, "To study the effects of interactive manipulation of videotaped evidence on credibility".
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) - Grant G94334 - Center for Communications Policy, 1994-1997 (Box 72, Folder 7)
    Jeffery Cole, "To develop a Center for Communications Policy".
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) - Grant G94334 - Center for Communications Policy, 1994-1997 (Box 73, Folder 1)
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) - Grant G94335 - Paid political advertising, 1994-1996 (Box 73, Folder 2)
    Shanto Iyengar, "Continued research on paid political advertising".
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) - Grant G98221 - Study of internet and American society, 1998 (Box 73, Folder 3)
    "To hold a conference in order to plan how to carryout a longitudinal study examining how the American social fabric is changing because of computers and the internet in a rigorous and scientific way".
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) - General, 1978-1989 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) - General, 1990-1992 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) - General, 1993-1997 (Box 73, Folder 6)
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) - Media effects of political attitude, Paul Halpern, 1969-1976 (Box 73, Folder 7)
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) - School of Law, 1971-1974 (Box 73, Folder 8)
  - University of California, Los Angeles (UCLA) - Rod Gorney, Psychiatry, 1975-1977 (Box 74, Folder 1-2)
  - University of California, San Diego (UCSD) - General, 1972-1988 (Box 74, Folder 3)
  - University of California, San Diego (UCSD) - Moshe Cohen, Electronic network, 1983 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  - University of California, San Diego (UCSD) - George Colburn, Courses by Newspaper project, 1976-1978 (Box 74, Folder 5)
  - University of California, San Diego (UCSD) - Donald Norman, Cognitive science, 1987-1988 (Box 74, Folder 6)
  - University of California, Santa Barbara (UCSB), 1996-1997 (Box 74, Folder 7)
  - University of California, San Francisco (UCSF), 1974-1985 (Box 74, Folder 8)
  - University of California, Santa Cruz, 1971-1976 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  - University of California, Riverside (UCR), 1996 (Box 74, Folder 10)
  - The California Channel, 1992-1997 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  - California Institute of the Arts (CalArts), 1983-1995 (Box 74, Folder 12)
  - California Institute of Technology (Caltech) - Grant G96016 - Hyperforum software, 1996-1998 (Box 75, Folder 1-3)
    "To design, build and demonstrate computer software that will allow many people to participate in a 'forum' on a complex policy problem".
  - California Institute of Technology (Caltech) - Grant D96101 - New information technologies workshop, 1996-1998 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    "To conduct a workshop concerning the long term implications of new information technologies".
  - California Institute of Technology (Caltech) - Grant D96212 - 'New Information Technology for Collective Visualization of the Future' conference, 1996-1998 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    "Funds for a workshop planned for, 'New Information Technology for Collective Visualization of the Future'".
  - California Institute of Technology (Caltech) - General, 1969-1991 (Box 75, Folder 6)
  - California Institute of Technology (Caltech) - General, 1992 (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - California Institute of Technology (Caltech) - General, 1995-1996 (Box 75, Folder 8)
  - California Institute of Technology (Caltech) - Hyperforum meeting, 1996 (Box 76, Folder 1)
  - California Institute of Technology (Caltech) - Visions of a Sustainable World conference, 1991 (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - California Institute of Technology (Caltech) - Bruce Murray, 1993-1995 (Box 76, Folder 3-4)
  - Call Interactive, 1992 (Box 125, Folder 1)
  - California State University and Colleges - General, 1974 (Box 125, Folder 2)
  - Cardoza School of Law - Yeshiva University (Monroe Price) (D96321) (Box 125, Folder 3)
  - Carnegie Commission on Science, Technology and Government, 1990-1993 (Box 125, Folder 4)
  - Carnegie Corporation of New York, 1969-1994 (Box 125, Folder 5-9)
  - The Carnegie Council, 1990-1995 (Box 125, Folder 10)
  - Carnegie Mellon University, 1982-1995 (Box 125, Folder 11-13)
  - Carnegie Mellon University - R. Dannenberg (D91215), 1990-1991 (Box 125, Folder 14-15)
  - Carnegie Mellon University - R. Dannenberg (D91103), 1990-1991 (Box 125, Folder 16-17)
  - Carnegie Mellon University - Piano Tutor (G91017), 1991-1992 (Box 125, Folder 19)
  - Carnegie Mellon University - Newell, Fain-Lehman (G90327), 1990-1993 (Box 125, Folder 20-21)
  - Carnegie Mellon University - R. Dannenberg (G90326), 1990-1991 (Box 125, Folder 22-23)
  - Carnegie Mellon University - Robert Kraut (D96215), 1995-1997 (Box 125, Folder 24-25)
  - Carnegie Mellon University - Piano Tutor, 1988-1993 (Box 125, Folder 26)
  - Carnegie Mellon University - Fain-Lehman (G93112), 1993-1995 (Box 125, Folder 27-28)
  - The Carter Center, 1977-1996 (Box 126, Folder 1-4)
  - The Carter Center - Emory University (D91330), 1991-1992 (Box 126, Folder 5-6)
  - The Carter Center - Emory University - Mickiewicz (G91110), 1990-1992 (Box 126, Folder 7-8)
  - The Carter Center - Emory University - Mickiewicz (G92224), 1992-1993 (Box 126, Folder 9-10)
  - The Cato Institute, 1989-1996 (Box 126, Folder 11)
  - CBS News, 1977-1991 (Box 126, Folder 12)
  - CD-ROM, 1988-1991 (Box 126, Folder 13)
  - Center for Assessment and Policy Development, 1997 (Box 126, Folder 14)
  - Center for Communications, Inc., 1987-1992 (Box 126, Folder 15)
  - Center for Community Change (DG99223), 1999 (Box 126, Folder 16)
  - Center for Governmental Studies - Westen (G96327), 1996-1997 (Box 127, Folder 1-4)
  - 2017:FA785:004 - The Democracy Network - Eye on the Presidency, VHS tape, 21:04 minutes (Box 2017:FA785:004)
    Open for research. Digital access copy currently unavailable. Please contact a RAC archivist for further instruction.
  - Center for Media Education, 1995 (Box 127, Folder 5)
  - Center for Media and Public Affairs - Lichter (D94218), 1994 (Box 127, Folder 6-7)
  - Center for Media and Public Affairs - Lichter (G94226), 1994-1995 (Box 127, Folder 8-9)
  - Center for National Independence in Politics (CNIP), 1991-1995 (Box 127, Folder 10)
  - Center for National Independence in Politics (CNIP) - Kimball (G92223), 1991-1993 (Box 127, Folder 11-12)
  - Center for National Independence in Politics (CNIP) - Kimball (G92110), 1991 (Box 127, Folder 13-14)
  - Center for National Independence in Politics (CNIP) - Kimball (G93335), 1993-1995 (Box 127, Folder 15-17)
  - Center for the New West, 1992-1997 (Box 127, Folder 18-19)
  - Center for Policy Alternatives, 1990-1993 (Box 128, Folder 1-3)
  - Center for Policy Research (Box 128, Folder 4-5)
  - Center for Policy Research - Etzioni (G92113), 1991-1993 (Box 128, Folder 6)
  - Center for Public Resources, 1978-1990 (Box 128, Folder 7-16)
  - Center for Public Resources - Board Material, 1985-1990 (Box 128, Folder 17-22)
  - Center for Strategic and International Studies, 1989-1993 (Box 129, Folder 1-2)
  - Center for the Study of Language and Information (Box 129, Folder 3)
  - Central Educational Network - James A. Fellows (D91102), 1990 (Box 129, Folder 4)
  - General: Ward Chamberlain, 1992 (Box 129, Folder 5)
  - Peggy Charron - Action for Children's Television, 1986-1991 (Box 129, Folder 6-7)
  - University of Chicago - L. Lessig (96-3106), 1996 (Box 129, Folder 8)
  - Children's - Miscellaneous, 1987-1991 (Box 129, Folder 9)
  - The Children's Museum, 1991 (Box 129, Folder 10)
  - The Children's Partnership, 1994-1996 (Box 129, Folder 11)
  - The Children's Partnership - Lipper (DG99217), 1998-1999 (Box 129, Folder 12)
  - Forrest Chisman and Other Matters, 1981-1990 (Box 129, Folder 13-19)
  - Claremont Colleges (Citizen's Jury), 1990-1995 (Box 130, Folder 1-7)
  - The Edna McConnell Clark Foundation, 1971-1992 (Box 130, Folder 8)
  - Classroom, Inc., 1991-1996 (Box 130, Folder 9-13)
  - Jim Clark, 1986-1990 (Box 130, Folder 14)
  - Clemson University - James Simmons, 1997 (Box 130, Folder 15)
  - Hillary Rodham Clinton - Correspondence, 1993 (Box 130, Folder 16)
  - The College Board, 1985-1994 (Box 130, Folder 17-18)
  - University of Colorado, Boulder - Tracey (D91107), 1989-1992 (Box 130, Folder 19)
  - University of Colorado, 1987-1996 (Box 130, Folder 20-26)
  - Columbia University - Center for Telecommunications, 1988 (Box 131, Folder 1)
  - Columbia University - School of Journalism - Konner, 1988 (Box 131, Folder 2)
  - Columbia University - School of Journalism - Konner (D97106), 1996-1997 (Box 131, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University - School of Journalism - Konner (D96323), 1995-1997 (Box 131, Folder 4)
  - Columbia University - School of Journalism - Konner (D96214), 1994-1997 (Box 131, Folder 5)
  - Columbia University - Teachers College - Timpane (D92327), 1992-1993 (Box 131, Folder 6)
  - Columbia University, 1972-1996 (Box 131, Folder 7-13)
  - Columbia University - Bureau of Applied Social Resources, 1971 (Box 131, Folder 14)
  - Columbia University - Freedom Forum - Media Studies Center, 1992-1995 (Box 131, Folder 15)
  - Columbia University - School of Journalism - Alfred Dupont Awards, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 16)
  - Columbia University - Gannett Center for Media Studies, 1985-1986; 1990 (Box 131, Folder 17-20)
  - Columbia University - Graduate School of Business, 1989-1994 (Box 131, Folder 21-22)
  - Columbia University - Graduate School of Journalism, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 23)
  - Columbia University - School of Journalism, 1992-1996 (Box 131, Folder 24)
  - Columbia University - Graduate School of Journalism - Seminars on Media and Society (Fred Friendly), 1990 (Box 131, Folder 25)
  - Columbia University - Institute for Tele-Information Seminar, 1993 (Box 131, Folder 26)
  - Columbia University - Center for Telecommunications and Information Studies, 1989-1991 (Box 131, Folder 27)
  - Columbia University - CITI - Columbia Institute for Tele-Information, 1991-1992 (Box 131, Folder 28)
  - Columbia University - Center for Telecommunications, 1990 (Box 131, Folder 29)
  - Columbia University - Center for Telecommunications - Ely Noam, 1985-1990 (Box 131, Folder 30)
  - Columbia University - Teachers College, 1981-1995 (Box 132, Folder 1-2)
  - Columbia University - Arden House Conference, 1973 May 14 (Box 132, Folder 3)
  - Columbia University - Arden House Conference, 1973 May 29 (Box 132, Folder 4)
  - COMEX - General, 1991 (Box 132, Folder 5)
  - Comment, 1979-1980 (Box 132, Folder 6)
  - Committee for the Study of the American Electorate, 1996-1997 (Box 132, Folder 7)
  - Conference on Campaign Reform, 1994 July 29-30 (Box 132, Folder 8)
  - Committee for the Study of the American Electorate, 1990-1995 (Box 132, Folder 9-11)
  - Committee to Protect Journalists, 1991 (Box 132, Folder 12)
  - Committee for Economic Development, 1988-1990 (Box 132, Folder 13)
  - Common Cause, 1994 (Box 132, Folder 14)
  - Commonwealth Fund, 1985-1996 (Box 132, Folder 15-20)
  - Commutarian Movement - Surdna - Markle Supported (May 1992 Dinner and Seminar), 1992-1993 (Box 132, Folder 21)
  - Community Network, 1989-1993 (Box 132, Folder 22-26)
  - Owen Comora, 1992-1996 (Box 133, Folder 1)
  - Owen Comora - Public Relations Activities - Agreement, 1992-1994 (Box 133, Folder 2)
  - Computer Science and Telecommunications Board - Blumenthal, 1996 (Box 133, Folder 3)
  - Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility, 1990-1991 (Box 133, Folder 4-5)
  - Computer Professionals for Social Responsibility - Rotenberg (D94106), 1992-1994 (Box 133, Folder 6)
  - Computer Software, 1988 (Box 133, Folder 7)
  - Computing Research Association - Weirgarten, 1992 (Box 133, Folder 8)
  - Computers - Adapso - Burton Grad, 1986-1987 (Box 133, Folder 9)
  - The Concord Coalition, 1992-1996 (Box 133, Folder 10)
  - Concord Commission, 1992 (Box 133, Folder 11)
  - The Conference Board, 1990 (Box 133, Folder 12)
  - Conferences - General, 1974-1990 (Box 133, Folder 13)
  - University of Connecticut Foundation - Yankelovich (D95321), 1995-1998 (Box 133, Folder 14)
  - Eileen Connell, 1988-1989 (Box 133, Folder 15)
  - Connor Communication, 1994 (Box 133, Folder 16)
  - Consumer Interest and Research Institute, 1982-1992 (Box 133, Folder 17)
  - The Contact Center Network - Ami Dar (D97104), 1996-1998 (Box 133, Folder 18)
  - Coopers and Lybrand, 1994 (Box 133, Folder 19)
  - Coporation for Public Broadcasting, 1990-1996 (Box 133, Folder 20)
  - Corporation for Society, 1991-1992 (Box 133, Folder 21)
  - Cosmic Campus, 1992-1993 (Box 133, Folder 22)
  - Cosmic Campus - Bergland, 1992 (Box 134, Folder 1-2)
  - Council on Foreign Relations - Zemmol (D93101), 1992-1993 (Box 134, Folder 3)
  - Council on Foundations - Joseph (D92331), 1993 (Box 134, Folder 4)
  - Council on Foundations - Joseph (D92221), 1992 (Box 134, Folder 5)
  - Council on Foundations - Joseph (D91323), 1991 (Box 134, Folder 6)
  - Council on Foundations - Joseph (D91214), 1991 (Box 134, Folder 7)
  - Council on Foundations - Buhl (D90321), 1990 (Box 134, Folder 8)
  - Council on Foundations - Ridings (D98219), 1998 (Box 134, Folder 9)
  - Council on Foundations - Ridings (D97216), 1996-1998 (Box 134, Folder 10)
  - Council on Foundations - Joseph (D96107), 1996-1997 (Box 134, Folder 11)
  - Council on Foundations - Joseph (D95212), 1995 (Box 134, Folder 12)
  - Council on Foundations - Joseph (D94316), 1994-1995 (Box 134, Folder 13)
  - Council on Foundations, 1988-1996 (Box 134, Folder 14-22)
  - Crossover Technologies, 1994-1996 (Box 135, Folder 1-8)
    Including Reinventing America (REUS) and Presidential '96 projects.
  - Cultural Collaborative (97-3298), 1996 (Box 135, Folder 9)
  - D - General, 1975-1995 (Box 135, Folder 10-15)
  - Daedalus, 1992-1993; 1996 (Box 135, Folder 16-19)
  - The Charles A. Dana Foundation, 1991-1993 (Box 135, Folder 20)
  - Dartmouth-Hitchcock Medical Center, 1990-1996 (Box 135, Folder 21)
  - Robert Davidson, 1990-1994 (Box 135, Folder 22-23)
  - Decision Labs, Ltd (Speedback) (Box 135, Folder 24)